蓝光电影网
blu-raydisc.tv
你是否曾觉得所做的一切都无济于事
Do you ever feel like nothing you do matters?
就像你在沙滩上留下了脚印
You leave footprints on the beach,
可第二天就会消失不见
and tomorrow they're gone.
日复一日过着平淡的生活
Like it's just today over again.
他们说青春年少的时光
They say your teen years
是用来广交朋友  纵情享乐的
are for making friends and having fun...
这让我感觉更难受了
which made me feel even worse.
艾米  我是杰克
Hey, Amy. It's Jake.
我们一起上数学课
I'm in your math class.
别忘了你的成人纸尿裤
Hey, don't forget your adult diapers.
是啊
Yeah, right.
杰克  有你的电话
Jake. Phone for you.
但那一天  一切都改变了
But that day, everything changed.
谢谢你送我  谢莉
Thanks for the ride, Shelley.
为什么要你去照顾你爷爷
So, how come you have to go deal with your grandpa?
我爸工作脱不开身
My dad couldn't get out of work.
我都不知道他居然有工作
I didn't think he worked.
我给爷爷打个电话
I'm just gonna call Grandpa.
你好  我是亚伯
Hello, this is Abe.
我是杰克
Hey, it's Jake.
不  不要过来  听我说
No! Don't come here. Listen to me.
这里不安全
It's not safe.
不要来这里
Stay away.
爷爷  你今天吃药了吗
Grandpa, did you take your pills today?
我枪柜的钥匙本来放在抽屉里
The key to my gun cabinet, it was in the drawer.
可是现在不见了
And now it's gone.
对啊  爸爸拿走了  记得吗
Yeah, Dad took it, all right?
他帮你保管着呢  没事的
For safekeeping. It's okay.
你爸要我赤手空拳对付他们吗
Your father wants I should fight them without a gun?
上帝保佑他
God bless him.
他怎么了  老年痴呆症吗
What's his deal, Alzheimer's?
障碍性痴呆症
Dementia.
那家伙真是吓死我了
That guy gave me the heebie-jeebies.
有事就叫我
Holler if you need me.
爷爷
Grandpa?
谢莉
Shelley!
怎么了
What's goin' on?
有人闯进去过
Someone broke in.
我车里有把38毫米口径的手枪  你在这儿等着
I've got a .38 in my car. You wait there.
爷爷
Grandpa!
911  请问您有什么紧急情况
911. What's your emergency?
911吗  我需要医护人员
911? Yeah, I need the paramedics.
地址是棕榈圈2040号  我爷爷...
It's at 2040 Palm Circle. My grandpa...
先生  请问您有什么紧急情况
Sir, what's your emergency?
爷爷
Grandpa.
你必须离开这里
You have to get away from here.
先生  能听见我说话吗
Sir, can you hear me?
快走  听我说
Please. Listen.
去岛上
Go to the island.
先生  医务人员已经出发了
Sir, paramedics are on their way.
找到埃莫森
Find Emerson.
那张明信片
The postcard.
去时光圈
Go to the loop.
1943年9月3号
September 3rd, 1943.
没事的
It's okay.
不要动  救护车马上就来了
Just don't move. There's an ambulance coming.
我知道你觉得我疯了
I know you think I'm crazy.
但那只鸟会向你解释清楚一切的
But the bird will explain everything.
你愿意去吗  泰利斯库  向我保证
Will you do this, Tygrysku? Promise me?
我保证
I promise, yes.
我以为我能保护你
I thought I could protect you.
几年前我就该告诉你
I should have told you years ago.
爷爷  告诉我什么
Grandpa. Tell me what?
爷爷
Grandpa!
谢莉  小心身后
Shelley, behind you!
那里根本没人
There was no one there.
容我说一句  杰克
May I say, Jake...
考虑到案发只过了一个月
that considering this was only a month ago...
你现在的状态已经非常好了
I think you're doing exceptionally well.
虽然我是个疯子
Apart from being crazy?
做噩梦和感到焦虑并不代表你是个疯子
Having nightmares and anxiety doesn't make you crazy.
那总是看到本不存在的事物呢
What about seeing things which aren't there?
其实  遭遇精神创伤后
Actually, in traumatic situations,
很容易出现这种情况
it's not at all uncommon.
你的潜意识会将电影中的画面或是...
Your subconscious mind drew an image from a movie or...
是故事
It was a story.
我小时候爷爷给我讲了很多故事
My grandpa told me stories when I was a kid...
关于他在战争中对抗过的那些怪物
about monsters that he fought in the war.
就是这样
So there you go.
他惨遭歹徒袭击
He was brutally attacked...
在你的脑海中  凶手毫无人性  是个怪物
and in your head, the man who did it was inhuman, a monster.
可他不是被人杀害的
It wasn't a man, though.
警察说是狗
The cops said that dogs
划破了纱门
scratched up the screen door...
他追它们追到了树林里
and he chased them off into the woods.
验尸官说他当时是心脏病突发
And the coroner said he had a heart attack.
警察说...
And the cops said...
狗吃了他的眼睛
that dogs go for the soft parts.
他们对那把叉子做了检测
They DNA tested the fork...
上面有动物DNA
and it had animal DNA.
案子就这么结了
So, that's case closed.
他似乎是一位很优秀的绅士
He sounds like an extraordinary gentleman.
你和他亲近吗
Were you very close?
波多黎各
Puerto Rico.
这里
Here.
这里有一片湖  会在黑夜中发光
There's a lake where the water glows in the dark.
还有一个秘密隧道
And a secret tunnel.
我就是在那里躲避怪物的
That's where I hid from the monsters.
他以前经常照看我
He used to babysit me a lot.
和爷爷在一起时  我会觉得自己很特别
When I was with him, I felt special.
我的鸭肉火候又过了
My duck was dry again.
亚伯  都11点了  他怎么还没睡
Abe. It's, like, 11:00. What is he doing up?
我要做一个探险家
I'm gonna be an explorer.
爷爷在帮我计划我的首次出航
Grandpa's helping me plan my first voyage.
孩子  世界上的一切已经都被探索出来了
Everything's already been discovered, buddy.
它们威胁彼此
They terrorize each other...
然后肆意破坏了岛屿其他部分
before wreaking havoc on the rest of the island.
别听你爸的
Pay no attention to your father.
他啥都不懂
He knows bubkes.
来吧  泰利斯库  该去睡觉了
Come, Tygrysku. Off to bed.
它们从不挑食
And they're not choosy.
总是成群结队地撕碎食物
These talons come in squadrons.
触地得分  佛罗里达  太激动人心了
Touchdown, Florida! What a drive.
你能给我讲个故事吗
Can you tell me a story?
老规矩吗
The usual?
好  很久很久以前
Okay. Once upon a time...
有一个小男孩...
there was a little boy...
要带图片
With the pictures.
图片
Pictures.
很久很久以前
Once upon a time...
有一个叫亚伯的小男孩
there was a little boy called Abe.
就是你啊
That was you.
就是我
That was me.
他住在威尔士附近的一个小岛上
And he lived in a lovely children's home
住在一个温馨的儿童之家里
on a little island near Wales...
那里的阳光每天都很灿烂
where the sun shone every day.
那里的校长  佩格林小姐
The headmistress, Miss Peregrine...
非常聪明
was very clever.
她总是叼着烟斗
And she smoked a pipe.
她可以变成鸟
She could turn into a bird.
那里是专为特殊的孩子设立的...
It was a home for special children...
比如布朗温和维克多
like Bronwyn and Victor.
他们俩身体健硕  力能扛鼎
They were both as strong as 10 men.
还有休...
And Hugh...
休的身体里住着蜜蜂
Hugh had bees living inside him.
那艾玛呢
Where's Emma?
她可以飘浮
She could float.
她比空气还要轻
She was lighter than air.
必须穿特制的铅鞋
She had to wear special shoes made of lead
才不至于飘走
to keep her from floating away.
她现在在哪儿
Where is she now?
我觉得她应该还在岛上
She's still on the island, I believe.
我的父母送我去那里
My mama and papa sent me there...
和那些特殊的孩子一起生活
to live with the special children.
而你呢  泰利斯库  该睡觉啦
And now, Tygrysku, time for sleep.
他以前总叫我泰利斯库
He used to call me Tygrysku.
是波兰语"小老虎"的意思
It's Polish for "Little tiger."
简直是史上最不恰当的昵称
He couldn't have picked a less appropriate nickname.
我一直是个胆小鬼
I was always a chicken.
你爸妈为什么要把你送走
Why did your mom and dad send you away?
我们在波兰生活的地方并不安全
Well, where we lived in Poland, it wasn't safe.
那里有怪物
There were monsters.
什么样的怪物
What kind of monsters?
有着长手臂的巨型怪物
Huge ones, with long arms...
没有眼睛
and no eyes...
还长着这样的触手
and tentacles like this.
最愚蠢的是
The dumb thing was...
这么多年来  我一直相信着他讲的故事
for years, I actually believed his stories.
这是米勒德  他是隐形的
And this is Millard. He's invisible.
老师说这些只是加了特效的照片
My teacher says they were trick photos.
那你相信她吗
And did you believe her?
爸爸说你大概是旅行时
Dad says you probably found them
在某家旧货商店里
at a junk store someplace...
找到了这些照片
when you went traveling.
我绝不会骗你  小老虎
I would never lie to you, Tygrysku.
但关于儿童之家和那些怪物  你骗了我
But you did, about the home, the monsters.
爸爸告诉我了
Dad told me.
你父亲非常清楚
Your father knows very well
我在儿童之家生活过
I went to live in the children's home.
他说在波兰确实有怪物
He said there really were monsters in Poland...
只不过他们没有长触手
just not the kind with tentacles.
他说你被送到威尔士是因为有坏人作乱
He said you got sent to Wales 'cause there were bad people.
那些坏人想杀掉任何与众不同的人
People who wanted to kill anyone who was different.
我不想再聊这个话题了
I don't wanna talk about this anymore.
他说那些孩子们确实很特别
He said the children were special...
但并不像你所说的那样
but not the way you said.
我只是想说  明天我本来计划要写作的
I'm just saying, tomorrow was supposed to be a writing day.
你已经花了五年时间写那本破书
Five years and counting on that damn book.
你儿子明天生日  你抽一天陪陪他
And taking one day to be with your son on his birthday...
能有什么大不了的
is gonna be a big difference?
好吧
Fine.
找到什么好东西了吗
You find something good?
快看这张照片  真是棒极了
Oh, look at that. That's awesome.
你应该带着
You should take that.
来吧  伙计  我们走吧
Come on, buddy, let's roll.
你怎么能如此淡定
How are you so okay?
杰克  我跟他没有你们那么亲近
Jakey, you were a lot closer to him than I ever was.
他是位很了不起的爷爷
He was a wonderful grandpa...
但却不是位称职的父亲
but not such a great dad.
他的工作
Never seemed to pick a job...
经常要加班到深夜
that didn't involve late nights
或者出差很久
or long trips away, though.
我和你苏茜姑姑总觉得
Me and Aunt Susie always kind of thought
他也许背着你奶奶出轨了
he was, maybe, cheating on our mom.
抱歉  伙计  我知道你有多崇拜他
I'm sorry, buddy. I know how much you worshiped him...
但事实就是这样
but there it is.
惊不惊喜
Surprise!
生日快乐  杰克表哥
Happy birthday, Cousin Jake!
小杰  你能来一起过暑假实在太好了
J-dog, it's great you're coming to spend a summer with us.
回头给你看看我们的新船
Wait till you see the new boat.
真是迫不及待
Can't wait.
是我  苏茜姑姑
It's Aunt Susie.
我觉得你应该挺想打开看看
Thought you might wanna open this one.
是你爷爷留给你的
It's from your grandpa.
我整理他的遗物时发现的
Found it while I was packing up.
我觉得他大概是打算某一天交给你
I figured he meant to give it to you someday.
谢谢
Thanks.
致杰克  以及他尚未探索的那些世界
To Jake, and the worlds he has yet to discover.
我最亲爱的亚伯
My dearest Abe...
希望你收到明信片时一切安好
I hope this card finds you well.
我和孩子们非常渴望听到你的最新见闻
The children and I yearn to hear your news.
希望不久的将来你能再回来看看我们
I do hope you will visit us again soon.
我们非常想念你
We should so love to see you.
羡慕你的
With admiration...
阿尔玛·佩格林
Alma Peregrine.
寄出时间才过了两年
Hmm. Only two years ago.
我猜她应该还活着
I suppose it's possible she could still be alive.
没错
Right.
我可以去见见她
I could meet her.
也许甚至能搞清楚爷爷
Maybe even find out what it was
到底想让我们知道什么
Grandpa wanted me to know.
如果她死了呢
But what if she's dead?
戈兰医生
Dr. Golan...
我们非常担心
we are very concerned
杰克目前的精神状况
with Jake's state of mind right now.
我不可能放下手头的一切
There's no way I'm putting my life on hold
带你去威尔士
to take you to Wales.
爸爸可以带我去
Dad could take me.
他还可以观察鸟类
And he can look at birds...
写写书
and work on his book.
你也可以休息一下
It means you get a break.
正如戈兰医生所说
As Dr. Golan said...
也许这样我就能放开了
maybe I can move on.
放下过去的一切
Like, closure.
让他亲眼见一下这个儿童之家
Having an opportunity to see this children's home...
把现实和幻想分开
and separate fantasy from reality...
也许会有所帮助
may be helpful.
最起码
And at the very least...
这样的旅程可以给他机会
a trip like this provides a chance to...
与过去告别
say goodbye.
"凯恩霍尔姆岛  人口92"
"Cairnholm. Population of 92.
"这里最出名的地方是"
"Best known for its proximity...
"1915年遇难的奥古斯塔游轮"
"to the final resting place of the cruise liner Augusta...
"沉没点在附近"
"which sank in 1915.
"岛上只有一家酒店"
"There is just one hotel..."
就是我们要住的
That's us.
是啊  希望那里有波旁威士忌
Yeah. I hope there's bourbon.
杰克  快看
Jake, check it out.
那是只游隼
That's a peregrine falcon.
一只游隼  跟儿童之家校长名字一样啊
A peregrine, like the headmistress?
好吧
Sure.
你爷爷大概就是根据这个名字
That's probably where Grandpa came up
编出了校长能变成鸟的故事
with that whole turning into a bird thing.
又或者  也许那真的是她
Or maybe, maybe that's really her!
佩格林小姐
Hey, Miss Peregrine.
是我  杰克
It's me, Jake.
我是亚伯·波特曼的孙子
I'm Abe Portman's grandson.
请不要在我们头上拉屎
Please don't crap on us.
天哪  爸  我开玩笑的
Oh, my God. Dad, I'm kidding.
怎么回事  有人吗
What the... Hello?
有人吗
Hello?
有人在吗
Anybody home?
你们知道酒店经理在哪里吗
Any idea where I'd find the manager of this place?
正是在下  抱歉让你久等了
That's me. Sorry to keep you.
我刚推奥吉叔叔上厕所去了
Just helping Uncle Oggie to the loo.
我叫凯夫  楼上有房间
I'm Kev. There's room upstairs.
好极了
Oh, great.
我去去就回
I'll be back in a bit.
好的
Okay.
凯夫去给我们准备套房了
Kev's just getting our suite ready.
等房间准备好之前
Um, while we're waiting...
我们可以去海滩上看看
I thought maybe we could go check out the beach.
之前不是说去儿童之家吗
I thought we would go to the children's home.
鸟是在海滩边筑巢吗
Is the beach where the birds nest?
我觉得我们可以快速去看一下
I thought we could just check it out real quick.
我可以自己去儿童之家
I could go to the home by myself.
这样你就可以慢慢享受看鸟的时光了
Then, you can really take your time and enjoy it.
拜托  杰克  你妈肯定不让
Come on, Jakey. You know your mom would freak.
要是我找人带我一起去呢
What if we can find someone to take me?
伙计们
Hey, dudes.
-爸  别  -嘘  我来搞定
- Dad. Don't. - Shh! I got this.
我想问问你们谁有兴趣
I was just wondering if any of you guys...
帮忙给我儿子带带路
might be interested in taking my son here
他想去岛的另一边
to the other side of the island.
你们叫什么
So, what are your names?
我是虫仔  这是说唱歌手污迪
I'm Worm. This is MC Dirty D.
说唱歌手污大佬
MC Dirty Bizniz.
你不是改了名字吗
I thought you changed it.
没有
No.
不  你改了  记得吗
No, you did, remember?
露丝说"污大佬"
When Ruth said "MC Dirty Bizniz"
听起来像是拉裤子里了
made it sound like you cacked your trousers.
但是她说"污迪"听起来就像
Yeah, but she said "Dirty D" Sounded like
有个人卫生问题
a personal hygiene problem.
等等  这些是外号还是...
Wait. Are these, like, nicknames, or...
艺名  我们是威尔士最屌的说唱歌手
Stage names. We're the sickest rappers in Wales.
来  虫子  给美国佬秀一个
Go on, Worm. Show this Yank how it's done.
什么  现在吗
What? Now?
*我总在神父洞里烂醉如泥*
*I like to get wrecked down the Priest Hole*
*你爸来这里是因为他一贫如洗*
*Your dad's always here 'cause he's on the dole*
*我们的韵律  紧凑而随意*
*Our rhymes are tight yet I make it look easy*
*我们的节拍  让人啧啧称奇*
*Our beats are hot like chicken jalfrezi*
好吧  挺好的
Oh, yeah, no. It's good.
我们抄近路吧  迪
Should we take the shortcut, D?
这样节省时间  听我的
We'll get there quicker. Take it from me.
从什么下去吗
What, down here?
是的
Yeah.
走吧
Go.
这边吗
This way?
怎么回事...
What the...
这真的是去儿童之家的路吗
Is this even the way to the children's home?
直走穿过树林
Right through those trees.
没必要计较已经脏了的鞋  小子
No use crying over a lost shoe, boy-o.
儿童之家  到底发生了什么
The children's home. What happened to it?
德国人的一场空袭  炸弹落在了屋顶
A German air raid. Bomb fell right on the roof.
1943年9月3日
September the 3rd, 1943.
后来他们去了哪里
Where did they go after?
校长和孩子们
The headmistress and the children.
没有幸存者  可怜的小家伙们
Not one survivor. Poor little buggers.
他们确实很可爱
And they were lovely, too.
为什么他没告诉我们  他们全死了
Why didn't he tell us that they all died?
他离开去参军  三个月后
He leaves to join the army, and 3 months later,
所有他认识的人都死了
everyone he knows gets killed?
即使是你爷爷也不会当作睡前故事讲给你
Not even Grandpa could turn that into a bedtime story.
难怪他总是不愿与儿子亲近
Well, no wonder he was scared of being a dad...
害怕与人深交
being close to anyone.
听着
Listen.
你得和人好好聊聊  儿子
You need to talk about all this with someone, buddy.
我们应该打给戈兰医生
We should call Dr. Golan.
看来今天是个好日子
Certainly some enjoyment today.
你同意我今天
Er, do you mind if I go hang out
和那些小伙伴出去吗
with those other kids today?
他们邀请我的
They asked.
是吗  那太好了
Yeah? That's awesome.
亚伯
Abe?
不
No!
你是艾玛
You're Emma!
还有双胞胎
And the twins.
奥利芙
And Olive.
布朗温
And Bronwyn.
他是米勒德
And he's Millard.
不  你们死了
No, you're dead.
你们全死了
All of you, you're all dead.
他虽然能隐  但他还是死了
He's invisible, but he's still dead.
我们没死
None of us are dead.
我的天哪  是不是我死了
Oh, my God. Am I dead?
没有
No.
在楼里的时候
You called me Abe.
你叫我亚伯  为什么
In the house. Why?
你看起来像他
You looked like him.
只是乍一看而已
Just for a moment,
后来你就开始尖叫
before you started screaming...
冲了出去  还把自己撞晕了
running away, and concussing yourself.
等等  发生了什么
Wait. What's happening?
我们要等到海岸没人的时候
We're waiting until the coast is clear...
回到时光圈
before we go into the loop.
永远不知道有谁会看到
You never know who might be watching.
等等  要回到哪里
Wait. Before we go into what?
拜托  杰克
Please, Jake.
佩格林小姐在等着  她在渡口看到你了
Miss Peregrine's waiting. She saw you on the ferry.
她叫我们来接你
She sent us to get you.
你这是要去哪里
Where do you think you're going?
回我的房间
To my room.
我是这儿的住客
I'm a guest here.
你觉得这里像旅馆吗
Does this look like a hotel to you?
是啊
Yeah.
我有钥匙
No. I've got a key.
你去问老板  他会告诉你
Talk to the manager. He'll tell you.
我就是老板  小子
I'm the manager, boy.
他是美国人  也许他是当兵的
He's American. Maybe he's army?
胡说
Bollocks.
听他这口音  真可怕
Listen to his accent. It's terrible.
他是间谍
He's a spy.
什么
What?
我不是  我只是游客
No, I'm not. I'm a tourist.
不如我们用老方法
I say we should get the truth out of him
逼他开口
the old-fashioned way.
趴下
Get down!
快来
Come on!
杰克  上来
Jake, get on!
快点  上来  小子
Come on! Get on, boy!
你们居然是真的  全是真的
I can't believe you're real. You're all real!
我们一直想告诉你
We have been trying to tell you.
不过我也有特殊能力
But I'm special, too.
什么
What?
在酒馆的时候  奥利芙  你看到了
In the pub. Olive, you saw.
是吧  那些瓶瓶罐罐都凭空飞来飞去
Right? Everything was flying and breaking.
是我干的
And that was me!
是我用意念控制的
I was doing it with my mind.
不  是我做的
No, that was me.
米勒德
Millard?
是的
Yeah.
你没穿衣服吗
Are you naked?
是的
Yeah.
我不明白...
I don't...
1943年一颗炸弹落到这里
A bomb dropped on you in 1943.
现在是1943年
It is 1943.
1943年9月3日
September the 3rd, 1943.
每一天都是
All day, every day.
这是我们的时光圈
It's our loop.
你们很准时
Right on time.
佩格林小姐  很高兴见到你
Miss Peregrine. Delighted to meet you.
我希望酒馆老板和警察
I do hope I'm not going to have the pub landlord
不要再来敲我家门
knocking on my door with the police again.
这个月我已经被迫杀他们两次
I've had to kill them twice this month.
真够麻烦的
It's been terribly inconvenient.
米勒德摔了一些东西  就这些
Millard broke a few things. That's all.
还有奥利芙大概放了一小把火
And Olive may have started a tiny fire.
可他们当时要伤害杰克
But they were going to hurt Jake.
瞧瞧你
Look at you.
上一次亲爱的亚伯寄给我的照片里
The last time dear Abe sent me a photograph...
你还是个小不点
you were just a tiny tot.
别傻站着  进来吧
Don't just stand there. Come in.
茶要凉了
Your tea's getting cold.
你怎么知道我在酒馆的
How did you know about the pub?
你大概有99斤重  对吧
You weigh approximately 109 pounds, correct?
我不...
I don't...
布朗温和双胞胎在你跑走后6分钟回来
Bronwyn and the twins returned 6 minutes after you ran away.
我还是没听懂
I think I'm missing something.
更何况
And quite apart from the fact
你觉得酒馆很安全
that the perceived safety of the pub...
所以最有可能往那里逃
makes it the most likely place to which you would flee...
你跑到那儿要十八分钟
it would take you 18 minutes to run there.
艾玛和米勒德驾着马车
Emma and Millard would have been moments behind...
紧随其后
on the horse and trap,
以13公里时速前进
traveling at 8.2 miles per hour.
考虑到在酒馆制造混乱的时间
Factoring in some sort of kerfuffle at the pub...
以及返回时因多了你的重量所费的时间
and the return journey with your added weight...
你们会在4点13分到达这里
you would arrive here at 13 minutes past 4.
那么  你的茶里要加糖吗
Now, then, do you take sugar?
可以了  谢谢你  奥利芙
That'll do. Thank you, Olive.
没人喜欢煮过头的茶水
Nobody enjoys over-boiled tea.
我帮你拿吧  伊诺克
Let me help you with those, Enoch.
不必了  不想耽误你的茶话会
Don't bother. Wouldn't want to interrupt your tea party.
节哀顺变  杰克
I'm so sorry for your loss, Jake.
你都知道了
You know, then.
我知道如果亚伯还活着
I know if Abe were alive,
他会提前告诉我你要来
he would have told me you were coming.
我们去外面喝吧
Shall we take our tea outside?
谢谢
Thank you.
他去世前  让我来找你
Before he died, he told me to find you.
他想让我知道一些事
There was something he wanted me to know.
他说你能解释一切
He said you could explain everything.
没错
That's absolutely true.
我无法解释的事情很少
There are very few things I can't explain.
我们通常被称作
We're what's known, in common parlance,
"异能者"
as "Peculiar."
迟了51秒  菲奥娜
51 seconds late, Fiona.
对不起  佩格林小姐
Sorry, Miss Peregrine.
晚饭您需要多少胡萝卜
How many carrots do you need for supper?
一根就行了
Just one will do.
就像我刚才说的  有些人是异能者
As I was saying, some people are peculiar.
这是一种家族遗传的隐性基因
It's a recessive gene carried down through families.
有时候很多代传承下来
Yet, many generations can pass
却没有一个异能者出现
without a peculiar child being born.
这么多年异能者一直饱受迫害
And alas, peculiars have been persecuted through the ages.
因此  我们在这样的地方生活
Hence, we live in places like this.
在威尔士吗
In Wales?
任何地方都可以  只要选对了日子
Anywhere will do if you pick the right day.
可以了  菲奥娜
That's fine now, Fiona.
我是被称作时鸟的异能者
You see, I'm a type of peculiar called an Ymbryne.
意思就是我可以...
That means I can...
你可以变成鸟
Yeah, you turn into a bird.
没错
I do. Yes.
但这个能力没什么用
But that's not very useful.
时鸟最主要的技能是控制时间
An Ymbryne's main skill is the manipulation of time.
我们会选择安全的地方  选安全的一天
We choose a safe place, a safe day...
创造一个时光圈
and create a loop.
什么意思
What do you mean?
一个时光圈能持续24小时
A loop preserves the last 24 hours.
重置一次  就能在里面多生活一天
Reset the loop, and the day is yours to live in again.
每天都重置
Reset it daily...
就能永远待在里面了
and you can stay there forever.
与世隔绝  绝对安全
Entirely safe from the outside world.
刚刚好  布朗温  好孩子
Right on time, Bronwyn. Good girl.
这就是为什么我们时鸟
And that's why we Ymbrynes
总是负责照顾孩子们
are charged with the care of the young.
而且大家都不会变老
And no one ever gets older.
这样对大家都好
It's best for everyone this way.
我向你保证
I assure you.
每一任时鸟都承诺
Every Ymbryne commits herself...
要创造并维护这样的地方
to the creation and upkeep of a place like this.
给异能者孩子一个家
A home for peculiar children.
你想捣乱吗
You wanna muck around?
你的蜜蜂
Your bees.
接着
Get it!
你见过双胞胎了
You met the twins.
这是克莱儿
This is Claire.
米勒德  传球  我们要一起踢
Millard, pass the ball. We're playing together.
米勒德你见过了
Millard you met.
快
Ugh. Come on!
那是休
And that's Hugh.
不许耍赖  休
Stop cheating, Hugh.
米勒德  你又犯规了
Millard, that's a foul again.
我没有  里夫
No, it wasn't. Ref?
如果你俩一定要边踢边吵
If you two can't play soccer without squabbling...
我宁愿你们别玩了
I do wish you wouldn't play at all.
你以为裁判是干什么的
Do you know what a referee is?
下午好  我是贺拉斯
Good afternoon. I'm Horace.
很高兴认识你
Delighted to meet you.
当心
Careful!
这里极度需要新鲜血液
We sorely need some new blood here.
顺便说句  衣服不错
Super shirt, by the way.
谢谢
Thanks.
再加把劲儿
Try harder.
艾玛你已经认识了
You know Emma, of course.
我想介绍的差不多了
And I think that's everyone.
布朗温不是有个哥哥吗
Didn't Bronwyn have a brother?
对  维克多在楼上
Yes. Victor's upstairs.
等等  伊诺克和奥利芙去哪儿了
Wait, where did Enoch and Olive go?
天知道
Heaven knows.
自从我们去救杰克  他就在生闷气
Enoch's been off sulking ever since we went out to get Jake.
佩格林小姐  门口来了个警察
Miss Peregrine, there's a policeman at the door.
他说是关于酒馆的事
He says it's about the pub!
回头跟你算账  艾玛
We'll discuss this later, Emma.
不是他们的错
It wasn't their fault.
老实说  他们只是想帮忙
Honestly, they were just trying to help.
谢谢
Thanks.
你没我想得那么怂
You're not as wet as I thought.
她不会真的杀人  对吗
She's not really gonna kill anyone, is she?
只要她能谈妥就不会
Not if she can talk her way out of it.
你能帮帮我吗
Would you help me with something?
一般是伊诺克帮我  但是...
Enoch usually does it, but like I said,
他现在躲起来生闷气了
he's off sulking somewhere.
是因为我吗
Is that because of me?
他的独占欲很强
He's possessive.
需要我帮你什么呢
So, what did you need help with?
我的一项日常杂务
One of my daily chores.
把松鼠宝宝送回树上
Put the baby squirrel back in the tree.
什么松鼠宝宝
What baby squirrel?
每天都会这样吗
That happens every day?
就像时钟一样准
Like clockwork.
你可以把绳子绕到我的腰上吗
Now, would you mind tying that rope around my waist?
好
Uh, yeah.
好的  答应我要牢牢抓紧
Right. Promise to hold on tight.
我差点搞砸了
I nearly messed that up.
亚伯第一次也是
Abe did, too, the first time.
以前这是他的工作
This used to be his job.
艾玛  我得告诉你一件事
Emma, I need to tell you something.
他去世了
He's dead.
我知道
I know.
佩格林小姐猜到了  她总是能猜对
Miss Peregrine guessed, and she's always right.
没关系
It's okay.
很早之前我就跟他道过别了
I said goodbye to him a long time ago.
你们曾经很亲密吗
Were you close?
我以为我们很亲密
I thought we were.
有那么一阵子
For a while.
大概是我误会了
But I suppose not.
请问  他也像你们一样吗
Can I ask, was he like you?
他跟你一样  杰克
He was like you, Jake.
我得去换衣服  快吃晚餐了
I need to go and change for supper.
你会和我们一起吃晚餐吗
Will you be dining with us?
我不能待太晚
I can't stay out late.
五点半吃晚餐
Supper's at 5:30.
那还真早
Uh... That is pretty early.
我们年龄不一
The fact we're not all eight years old
佩格林小姐也很是为难
seems to have eluded Miss Peregrine.
你可以穿亚伯的衣服
You can borrow some of Abe's clothes.
他的房间在阁楼上
His room's in the attic.
杰克
Jake!
来正式和伊诺克认识一下吧
Come and meet Enoch properly.
你肯定觉得自己格格不入吧
You must feel pretty out of place.
别担心
Don't worry.
我习惯了
I'm used to it.
不  我没有担心
No. I wasn't worried.
不过同为男人  给你一条忠告
Some advice for you though, man to man.
如果你只是因为喜欢艾玛就想留下
If you're thinking of staying just because you like Emma...
别费劲了
don't bother.
告诉你  几十年前她就发誓远离爱情了
You see, she swore off romance decades ago...
因为一次爱情让她心碎了
when she got her heart broken.
而且她永远不会改变心意  所以...
And she's never gonna change her mind. So...
伊诺克  我没有
Enoch, I wasn't...
你这是在干什么
What are you doing?
他很厉害吧
Isn't he amazing?
你做了什么
What did you do?
这个吗
This?
杰克  好玩的部分还没到呢
Jake, this isn't even the fun part.
想知道好玩的部分是什么吗
Do you want to see the fun part?
他们就像木偶
They're like puppets.
我说什么他们就做什么
Just do anything I tell them.
用人更好玩呢
It's even more fun with people.
你真该看看以前
You should have seen some of
他们在我父母葬礼上的表现
the epic battles they used to have...
堪称史诗般的战斗
at my parents' funeral parlor.
你还需要领带
You'll need a necktie.
我爷爷这些年远游都干什么了
So what did my grandpa do when he was traveling?
拜访其他时光圈
Visited other loops.
真的吗  去做什么
Really? To do what?
杰克  有些问题
Jake, there's some questions
我不能回答  好吗
that I can't answer, all right?
所以为了我好  请你...
So, it would be a lot easier for me if you just...
别再问了
stopped asking them.
你干什么呀
Hey! What are you doing?
米勒德
Millard.
去穿上衣服
Go and put some clothes on.
有礼貌的人是不会裸体上餐桌的
Polite persons do not take their supper in the nude.
好啦知道啦
All right. All right.
你可以坐这里  杰克
You can sit here, Jake.
快看伊诺克
Look at Enoch.
他吃醋了
He's jealous.
我为什么要吃醋
Why would I be jealous?
奥利芙就是嫁给他  我也无所谓
Olive can go marry Jake, for all I care.
别这么小气  伊诺克  她也不想嫁
Don't be mean, Enoch. She doesn't want to.
她只是因为来了客人很开心
She's just excited to have a visitor.
没有人要结婚
Nobody is marrying anybody.
趁饭还没凉赶紧吃吧
Now, eat up your food before it gets cold.
休
Hugh!
你的网呢
Where's your net?
休  你不能再这样了  休
Hugh! You have to stop doing this, Hugh.
快走开
Go away!
你肯定觉得很奇怪吧  杰克
Must be very strange for you, Jake.
见到了你祖父的朋友们
Meeting your grandfather's friends.
穿越到了另一个世纪
Visiting another century.
你们的世界里有飞船吗  杰克
Are there spaceships in your time, Jake?
像飞侠哥顿故事里写的那样
Like the Flash Gordon books.
好了  奥利芙
Now, now, Olive.
我不是说过吗  不要乱提问
What did I say about asking questions?
我们不探讨未来
We don't discuss the future here.
我们只享受过去的开心生活
We enjoy living in the good old here and now.
克莱儿  你怎么不吃
Claire, why aren't you eating?
因为杰克在  她不好意思
She's embarrassed in front of Jake.
不用  请随意
Don't be. Please.
杰克  你有什么特殊能力
So, Jake, what's your peculiarity?
我没有特殊能力
Oh, I'm not peculiar.
正因如此  朋友们
And that, my friends,
他不会留下
is why he will not be staying with us...
我们怎么劝他都没用
no matter how hard we try to persuade him.
我们说过这个问题了  杰克只是来做客
We've spoken about this. Jake is just visiting.
也许他想留下呢
He might want to stay.
你想留下对不对  杰克
Don't you want to stay, Jake?
你是说今晚  还是
Tonight? Or...
永远  你应该永远和我们在一起
Forever. You should stay forever.
他又不是不能走  为什么还要留下
Why would he, if he doesn't have to?
他可以活在外面的世界  慢慢变老
He can live out there, grow older...
不像我们  他能拥有幸福的一生
have a good time instead.
他会离开的  像他祖父一样
He'll leave, just like his grandfather did.
艾玛
Emma!
抱歉
Excuse me.
她要去哪里
Where's she going?
你有点过分了  伊诺克
That wasn't nice, Enoch.
你很清楚亚伯当初为什么离开
You know perfectly well why Abe left us.
他去参军
To join the army.
遇到了一位小姐  吃了结婚蛋糕
And then he met a lady, and had a nice wedding cake...
生了个可爱的孩子
and a lovely little baby.
孩子们
Children.
我知道你们都想认识新朋友
I know you'd all like a new friend...
但我想杰克在佛罗里达也有朋友
but I'm sure Jake has plenty of his own back in Florida.
我先去接电话
I think you should all get ready
大家准备进入电影时间吧
for movie time while I answer that.
你以前都让我们等你回来的
But you always let us stay for it.
喂  我是亚伯
Hello, this is Abe.
大家都好吗
How is everyone?
给你多加了棉花糖  杰克
Yours has extra marshmallows, Jake.
米勒德  穿上睡衣
Millard, put some pajamas on.
这里太热了
It's too hot in here.
别抱怨了
Stop moaning.
请让让
Excuse me.
我爷爷跟我讲过
My grandpa told me about this.
贺拉斯能投影他的梦  对吧
Horace projects his dreams, right?
他以前总听收音机
He used to listen to the radio.
把内容倒背如流了  也就没意思了
Gets tedious when you know every word off by heart.
真不错  我要了
Splendid. I'll take it.
他的梦大多都是关于衣服的
He dreams about clothes mostly.
很高兴认识你
Delighted to meet you.
顺便说句  衣服不错
Super shirt, by the way.
这是他什么时候梦到的
When did he dream this?
昨晚
Last night.
他的梦有时能够预言
Some of his dreams are prophetic.
但是  大多都会梦到衣服
But, mostly they're about clothes.
预言是指  能看到未来吗
Prophetic as in, he can see into the future?
时鸟  她是谁
An Ymbryne. Who is she?
佩格林小姐  你认识她吗
Miss Peregrine, do you know her?
别傻了
Don't be silly.
贺拉斯肯定只是做了个噩梦  没什么
Horace must have just had a bad dream. That's all.
就这样吧  谢谢你  贺拉斯
That's quite enough of that. Thank you, Horace.
我想我该走了
I should probably get going.
要是愿意  你可以在这里过夜
You could stay the night, if you wanted to.
不然还得摸黑走夜路回去
Rather than walk home alone in the dark.
但是岛上很安全的  不是吗
But the island is very safe, isn't it?
当然了
Of course!
我只是说路上有些崎岖
I only meant the path is dreadfully bumpy.
他可能会摔跤
Jake could trip.
不如你送他走小路
Perhaps you could show him the shortcuts.
这样他就不用摔跤了
Should he ever need to avoid bumps.
至少留下来看完重置吧  杰克
Won't you at least stay to see the reset, Jake?
真的特别壮观
It's really quite spectacular.
-就是  -留下嘛  杰克
- Yeah! - Stay, Jake!
快来  杰克
Come on, Jake!
*小兔子快跑  小兔子快跑*
*Run, rabbit, run, rabbit*
*跑跑跑*
*Run, run, run*
*别让农夫拍手叫好好好好*
*Don't give the farmer his fun, fun, fun*
*没有兔子派  他也过得很愉快*
*He'll get by without his rabbit pie*
*所以小兔子快跑  小兔子快跑跑跑*
*So run, rabbit, run, rabbit, run, run, run*
*小兔子快跑  小兔子快跑*
*Run, rabbit, run, rabbit*
*砰砰砰  那是农夫的枪声*
*Bang, bang, bang, bang goes the farmer's gun*
*别让农夫拍手叫好好好好*
*Don't give the farmer his fun, fun, fun*
*没有兔子派  他也过得很愉快*
*He'll get by without his rabbit pie*
太令人惊叹了
That was fantastic.
什么声音
What was that?
是我的手机
It was my phone.
在时光圈里一直没信号  现在有了...
It's been dead the whole time in the loop. I guess now...
手机
Your phone?
对  就像电话
Yeah. Like a telephone.
你可以打给别人
You can call people...
发送文字信息
send written messages.
等等  有个好功能
Wait, you'll love this.
你可以拿它拍照
You can take a picture.
按那个  那里  对
Press that, there. Yeah.
你看
See?
怎么了
What's wrong?
只是想到有一天你会长大
It's just funny to think that one day, you'll grow up.
就像亚伯一样
Like Abe did.
结婚生子
Get married, have children.
甚至有了孙辈
Grandchildren.
你可能还会给他们看这张照片
You might even show them this photograph.
而我还在这里
And I'll still be here.
你难道不能离开这里吗
Couldn't you leave some day?
如果你想的话  能不能活在当下
And live in the present, if you wanted to?
不
No.
在你的世界里  过不了几分钟
More than a few minutes in your time
我落下的那些年月就会补上
and the years would catch up.
你会变老
You would age?
我想它是贺拉斯梦里的那只时鸟
I think it's the Ymbryne from Horace's dream.
你确定这不是普通的鸟吗
Are you sure it's not just a bird?
我不知道  它难道不会变身吗
I don't know, wouldn't it change?
不能  受了伤就变不了
She can't. Not if she's hurt.
我得把她带回家  你走吧
I need to take her inside. You should go.
求你别说话了
Please don't say anything else.
我讨厌分别
I hate goodbyes.
我明天会回来的
I'll come back tomorrow.
不用急  我永远都在这里
There's no hurry. I'll be here forever.
我在这个破岛到处找你
I've been all over this damn island.
你跑哪儿去了
Where the hell were you?
我正在往回走
Um, I was just on my way back.
对不起  我没注意时间
I'm sorry. I lost track of time.
我跟虫仔和污迪玩得太开心了
I was having a blast with Worm and Dirty D.
污迪
Dirty D?
好吧
You know what?
这样很棒  很健康
This is good. This is healthy.
你交了奇怪的朋友
You're making weird friends...
做了青少年该做的事情
and doing teenage stuff.
我觉得这很正常
I think this is normal.
我想戈兰医生也会赞成的
I'm sure Doctor Golan will approve.
你们俩美国佬
Hey, you. American!
过来
Get over here.
看  他们也在
Oh, look. There they are.
污迪和虫仔
There's D-Bag and Worm Man.
是你们干的吗
Did you do this?
什么  不是
What? No.
当然不是
Of course not.
不是我们干的
It wasn't us.
先生  我不知道这里发生了什么
Listen, sir. I don't know what happened here.
但是我儿子和他朋友一整天都在一起
But my son and his friends have been together all day.
杰克绝不会做这种事情
Jake would never do anything like this.
胡说  我们今天根本没见过他
Bollocks! We haven't seen him!
你昨天是花钱请我们
You paid us yesterday.
我们怎么会免费跟他玩
Why would we hang out with him today for free?
杰克  你到底有没有和他们在一起
Jake? Were you with them or not?
没有  对不起
No. I'm sorry.
但你不会真以为我能做出这种事吧
But you don't seriously think I could do this?
先生  我们先走了
I think we're done here, sir.
你能给我捎个信吗
Can you pass on a message for me?
请你告诉戈兰医生
Can you tell Doctor Golan...
要不是她怂恿这次荒谬的旅行
that if she hadn't encouraged this cockamamie trip...
也许我儿子就不会
maybe my son wouldn't be
整天在一个废弃房子里待着
moping around all day in a derelict house...
待到整个人都神经崩溃了
having a goddamn breakdown!
人呢
Hello?
爸爸  我没有
Dad, I'm not.
我很好
I'm fine.
不  你不好
No. You're not.
你一点都不好  杰克
You're not fine, Jake.
我们就不应该来这里
Coming here was a terrible, terrible idea.
对不起我撒谎了  我只是想...
Look, I'm sorry I lied. I just wanted...
把你的闹钟设到早上8点
Just set your alarm for 8:00 a.m.
我想早点到海滩
I wanna get to the beach early.
然后就一起
The rest of the time we're stuck
待在这个破岛上
on this craphole island...
一刻也不分开
we're sticking together.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
下楼喝一杯
Downstairs for a drink.
亲爱的佩小姐
Dear Miss Peregrine...
我不想惊扰到你
I don't wish to alarm you...
这是我一个线人寄给我的
but one of my informants sent me this.
看来巴伦团队的一些成员
It would appear that some of Mr. Barron's group...
此刻正在英国黑池
are in Blackpool, England.
如果我没记错
If I recall...
艾沃赛特女士在那里有个时光圈
Miss Avocet has a loop there.
请提醒她  并建议她
Please warn her and suggest...
立刻重建一个时光圈
that she make a new one right away...
隐藏起来
well-hidden.
请你照顾好自己
And take the greatest care yourself.
爱你的亚伯
With love, Abe.
2016年1月
January, 2016.
准备好登陆海滩了吗
Who's ready to hit the beach?
我的天...
Oh, my...
难以置信
Unbelievable.
在巢区的正中间搭帐篷
Right in the middle of a nesting area?
什么蠢货会这么干
What kind of idiot does that?
其实主要的巢区在那边
Actually, the main nesting area is over there.
如果你有兴趣  我可以带你去看
I can show you if you'd like.
能遇到一位观鸟同好真是太棒了
It's marvelous to meet a fellow bird spotter.
我是约翰·拉蒙特
John Lamont.
我是富兰克林·波特曼  这是我儿子杰克
Franklin Portman. This is my son, Jake.
约翰·拉蒙特
John Lamont.
你的镜头真是太炫了
That's a hell of a camera you got there.
谢谢  确实相当棒
Oh, thanks. It's absolutely fantastic.
我来这里是为我的著作拍些照片
I'm here to do some snaps for a book I'm writing.
两位先生是来这里度假的吗
So, you gentlemen here on holiday?
真不幸  她的手臂跟鸟的翅膀一样
Unfortunately, her wings were flapping
上下摇摆
as much as the bird's!
我觉得你们想的
I think you fellas are
可能是另外一种"鸟"
thinking of another kind of bird.
你今天不去海滩了吗
So, you're not going to the beach today?
何必呢
What's the point?
既然那人要把凯恩霍尔姆岛
If that guy is gonna cover Cairnholm
写进他那浮夸高档的书里
in some big, glossy book...
肯定没人会看我的那本书了
no one's gonna even wanna look at mine.
还不如好好睡个午觉
Might just have a nice afternoon nap.
我猜你们今天早上
I don't suppose you saw Uncle Oggie
没在路上看到奥吉叔叔  是吗
on your travels this morning, did you?
通常这时候他应该到了
He's usually here by now.
我可以去找找他
I could go look for him.
你哪也不许去
You're not going anywhere.
杰克  你回来了  来和我们玩吧
Jake, you're back! Come and play!
我得去见佩小姐
I need to see Miss Peregrine first.
你知道她在哪吗
Do you know where she is?
经过那些黑暗的日子...
From the darkest days,
加拿大军队...
the Canadian army...
杰克  你回来了  太棒了
Jake. You're back. How wonderful!
它怎么样了
How's it doing?
艾玛说它是只时鸟
Emma said it was an Ymbryne.
是她  不是它
"She." Not "It."
时鸟总是女性
Ymbrynes are always female.
艾玛说得对
And Emma was quite correct.
这位是艾沃赛特女士
This is Miss Avocet.
她的时光圈在英国黑池
Her loop's in Blackpool. England.
你偷看了我的私人信件  杰克
That was a private letter, Jake.
巴伦先生是谁
Who is Mr. Barron?
佩小姐  如果我爷爷
Miss Peregrine, if my Grandpa
跟什么危险人物有纠葛
was involved with dangerous people...
我得告诉警察
I need to tell the police.
警察
Police?
你是说亚伯的死有蹊跷吗
Are you implying Abe died an unnatural death?
我发现他横尸在树林里
I found him in the woods...
双眼不见了
with his eyes missing.
这其中肯定有蹊跷吧
I'd say that was pretty unnatural.
若非必要  我绝不讨论令人不快的事
Unless essential, I don't discuss unpleasant matters.
时鸟的职责是保护孩子们  杰克
An Ymbryne's duty is to protect children, Jake.
我不是孩子
I'm not a child.
他想让你告诉我全部真相
He wanted you to tell me everything!
那你可真惨
Oh. How frustrating for you.
佩小姐有她的规矩
Between Miss Peregrine's rules...
而我的室友们又不想把你吓跑
and my housemates' little pact not to scare you off...
好像没人会告诉你真相
it's like no one's telling you anything!
那不如你来说吧
Why don't you, then?
反正你也不希望我留下
It's not like you want me here.
伊诺克  不行  你保证过的
Enoch, you can't. You promised.
奥利芙说得对
Olive's right.
不过我确实知道一个人
I do know someone who can get away
可以随意违反规矩
with breaking rules though.
你要不要去见他
Want to meet him?
伊诺克  别这样  求你了
Enoch, don't do this. Please!
你想跟我和杰克待在一起
You want to spend time with me and Jake,
你想让大家一起玩
we can all play together.
这是你说的
That's what you said.
这不是都在吗
Here we all are.
让开  奥利芙
Move, Olive.
你要是这样的话
If you're going to be like that,
我就不跟你做朋友了
then I don't want to be your friend.
伊诺克  你别去打扰维克多  布朗温会不开心
Enoch, leave Victor alone. It really upsets Bronwyn.
别吵吵了  菲奥娜
Stop fussing, Fiona.
你不觉得杰克应该跟每个人都见见吗
Don't you think Jake should meet everybody?
他想吓跑你  杰克
He's trying to frighten you away, Jake.
他以前总是嫉妒亚伯  现在又嫉妒你
He was always jealous of Abe. And now he's jealous of you.
你来跟我们一起玩吧
Come and play with us instead.
我挺想见见维克多的
I'd quite like to meet Victor.
你先请
After you.
你好  维克多
Hello, Victor.
我是杰克  抱歉打扰...
I'm Jake. I'm sorry to disturb...
他听不见的
Yeah, he can't hear you.
杰克你好  我是维克多
Hello, Jake. I'm Victor.
你想不想知道我是怎么死的
Do you want to know what killed me?
你来了  伊诺克跟你在一起吗
There you are. Is Enoch with you?
我们该去散步了
It's time for our daily walk.
艾玛  是谁杀了维克多
Emma, who killed Victor?
是不是那群白眼人
Was it the people with the white eyes?
我说过  你不要再提问了
I asked you not to ask questions.
我爷爷死的那天晚上我看到过一个
I saw one the night my grandpa died.
一个男人
A man.
如果真是这样
If it really was one,
你得告诉佩小姐
you have to tell Miss Peregrine.
你能从照片里认出他来吗
Could you recognize him from a photograph?
你有照片吗
Do you have one?
跟我来  我想一个人待着的时候会去那里
Come on. There's somewhere I go to be alone.
我在里面藏有东西
I have things there.
是这里吗
Is this the place?
不是  但是要从这里过去
No. This is how we get there.
艾玛  你的鞋
Oh! Emma! Your shoes!
是铅鞋
Lead shoes!
欢迎来到我的秘密基地
Welcome to my secret hideout.
你是怎么...
How did you...
用空气
Air.
这是我的异能
It's my peculiarity.
可以任意控制空气
It does what I want.
杰克
Jake...
你爷爷退役前...
before your grandfather retired...
让我帮他保管好这个
he asked me to keep this safe.
这是我爷爷的旧地图
This is my grandpa's old map.
上面会显示时光圈的位置
It shows you where the loops are.
就是他
That's him!
我看到的就是他
That's the man I saw.
-他是谁  -是巴伦
- Who is he? - That's Barron.
他是老大
He's the leader.
什么老大
The leader of what?
他们到底是什么人
Who are these people?
是坏人  暗黑异能者
Bad people. Bad peculiars.
亚伯穷其一生追捕着他们
Abe dedicated his life to hunting them down.
但他从未找到这些人
These are the ones he never found.
什么叫追捕
What do you mean, hunting?
他们会洗劫时光圈
They raided loops.
把里面的孩子赶尽杀绝
Whole homes full of children left for dead.
亚伯杀他们是为了救人
Abe took lives to save lives.
你出生后他才退休  他是为了保护你
He only retired when you were born to protect you.
保护我什么
From what?
如果我告诉你实情
If I tell you the rest,
你要保证不被吓跑
you have to promise not to run away.
杰克  你属于这里
Jake, you belong here.
你明知我不属于这里
You know I don't.
我跟你们不一样
I'm not like you.
我是普通人
I'm just ordinary.
不  你不是
No, you're not.
杰克
Jake...
只有异能者才能进入时光圈
only a peculiar can enter a time loop.
不  那不可能啊
No. That can't be right.
我应该能感觉到
I would know.
好
Fine.
那我给你看个别的东西
Then I'll show you something else.
快点  不然你就看不到了
Hurry. You'll miss it.
时鸟通常会选择好日子来制造时光圈
Ymbrynes usually pick the perfect day to create a loop.
但是佩小姐当时制造这个时光圈有点匆忙
But Miss Peregrine had to make this one in a rush.
为什么
Why?
因为当时德国人的炸弹就要掉下来了
Because the Germans were about to drop a bomb on the house.
重点在于
The point is...
1943年9月3日并不完美
September the 3rd, 1943 wasn't perfect.
杀死维克多的东西又回来了
The thing that killed Victor came back.
等等  小心
Wait! Watch out!
你会让她分心的
You'll put her off!
你能看到  对吗
You can see it, can't you?
别人都看不到
No one else can.
它是隐形的  杰克
It's invisible, Jake.
这是亚伯最厉害的天赋
That was Abe's greatest gift of all.
他能够看到那些怪物
He could see the monsters.
我们称之为虚空怪兽
We call them Hollowgast.
简称虚怪
Hollows for short.
我爷爷跟我讲过有人变成了怪物
My grandpa told me about people who turn into monsters.
说的就是他们吗
Is that what they are?
我会跟你解释一切  杰克
I will explain everything, Jake.
看来现在这成了我的责任
I fear it's my duty now, considering.
但你要明白  我这样做
But you should know that in doing so,
违背了我曾许下的郑重承诺
I'm breaking a solemn promise.
你出生时我就知道你是异能者
I knew you were peculiar when you were born.
但是你爷爷什么都不让我跟你说
But your grandfather forbid me to tell you anything.
他最大的愿望就是你能拥有平凡的童年
His dearest wish was for you to have an ordinary childhood.
我童年是够平凡的
I definitely had that.
他想等你成年之后再告诉你实情
He intended to tell you the truth when you turned 18.
希望他的睡前故事能够做个铺垫
He hoped his bedtime stories would pave the way.
我的书来了
Here's my book.
许多年前
Many years ago...
我们异能者出现了分化
a splinter faction emerged among our people.
有些异能者厌倦了时光圈内的生活  心生不满
Disaffected peculiars tired of living in loops.
也就是巴伦先生
That's Mr. Barron.
他认为只要想办法获取
He believed that by harnessing the essence
时鸟异能的精华
of an Ymbryne's powers...
他和他的同伙就能获得永生
he and his cronies could gain immortality...
并能在时光圈外生活
and be able to live outside loops.
他开始了一项实验
He devised an experiment.
他绑架了一只时鸟
He kidnapped an Ymbryne...
毫不关心
not knowing or caring
这次实验是否会危及她的生命
whether she would survive the experiment.
但巴伦和他同伙的命运
But the fate of Barron and his group
却更加骇人听闻
was more horrifying still.
巴伦为什么没变成怪物
Why didn't Barron turn into one?
他也变成了怪物
He did.
但是几年之后...
But years later...
他找到了一种逆转这种后果的方法
he found a way to reverse the effects.
重新变成人类
To regain humanity.
他们没有变成永生的神  而是变成了虚怪
They had become not immortal gods, but Hollows.
隐形的野兽  危险...
Invisible beasts, dangerous...
冷血  致命
cold-blooded, deadly.
记得我跟你说过他们洗劫了时光圈吗
Remember I told you they raided loops?
这就是原因
This is why.
巴伦发现了通过吸食
Barron discovered that by consuming
其他异能者的眼睛
the eyes of other peculiars...
特别是孩子们的眼睛...
especially children...
他就可以开始转化
he began to change.
吸食足够多的眼睛
Consume enough, and a Hollow
虚怪就能完全恢复人形
can fully regain its human form.
大家用餐愉快
Bon appetit.
就像巴伦和他的一些朋友所做的那样
Just as Barron and some of his friends did.
其他人只能继续做虚怪
The rest of them are stuck as Hollows.
你是说巴伦吃了我爷爷的...
Are you saying that Barron ate my grand...
他自己已经不需要眼睛了
He needs no more eyes himself.
但可能他让一只虚怪去找了你的爷爷  没错
But I fear he led a Hollow to your grandfather. Yes.
在时光圈第一次惨遭洗劫之后
After the first attacks on loops...
我们都更加善于隐藏和制造新的时光圈了
we all got better at hiding, making new loops,
对我们的行踪保密
keeping our whereabouts secret.
虚怪们日渐绝望
The Hollows grow more desperate every year...
而巴伦想要帮助他的朋友们
and Barron wishes to help his friends.
佩格林小姐  快来  艾沃赛特女士醒了
Miss Peregrine, come quickly. Miss Avocet's awake.
突然间  我又飞进去了
And suddenly, I flew into it again...
砰砰的两声  我什么都看不见了
Bang! Bang! I couldn't see anything.
佩格林小姐  他们发现了我的新时光圈
Oh, Miss Peregrine. They found my new loop.
孩子们  我想要救他们...
The children. I tried to save them...
但是虚怪太多了
but there were so many Hollows.
我不知道我是怎么逃出来的
I don't know how I escaped.
你现在安全了
You're safe now.
没人是安全的
None of us are safe.
他们在我的时光圈放置了机器
They set up the machine in my loop.
他们把它放在了黑池塔的地窖里
They put it in the cellars at Blackpool Tower.
他们还在那里
They're still there.
-他们的机器  -那个实验
- Their machine? - The experiment.
他们想再做一次
They intend to do it again.
这次  他要用更多时鸟
This time, he's using more Ymbrynes.
他仍然想得到永生
He still wants to be immortal.
虚怪们只攻击异能者吗
Do Hollows only attack peculiars?
当然不是
Of course not.
他们是怪兽  杰克
They're monsters, Jake.
他们对挡路者毫不留情
They'll slaughter anything in their path.
以前岛上有一些绵羊被杀了
Some sheep on the island were killed.
你认为他们还没到这里吗
You don't think they're here already, do you?
你见过白色眼睛的人吗
Have you seen anyone with white eyes?
我很抱歉  孩子们  我们不能待在这里了
I'm sorry, children. We can't remain here.
什么
What?
我们明天搭第一班渡轮离开小岛
We'll leave on the first ferry off the island tomorrow.
把重要物品打包
Pack anything of importance.
然后吃点三明治  早点睡觉
Then it's sandwiches and early to bed.
我们是要永远离开吗
Are we leaving for good?
-我们什么时候回来  -不回来了
- When are we coming back? - Never.
如果佩格林小姐明天晚上
If Miss Peregrine's not here
不在这里重置时光圈
to reset the loop tomorrow night...
这座房子就会被炸掉
the house gets bombed.
可我们的房子
But our house.
别哭
Don't cry.
佩格林小姐会在别的地方
Miss Peregrine will find you
给你们找一座漂亮的新房子
another lovely house, somewhere else.
一旦这个时光圈关闭了  就都结束了
Once this loop closes, that's it.
我没法回到自己的时代了
I can't get back to my own time.
你在那边看起来并不是很开心
You didn't seem very happy there.
我不能就这样走掉  我有家人
I can't just leave! I have a family!
而且你觉得自己很平凡
And you felt ordinary.
你无法改变任何事情
Like, nothing you do changes anything!
现在你有机会做点可以
Now you have a chance to do something
改变一切的事情
that changes everything!
杰克  我们现在有危险
Jake, we're in danger.
而你是唯一能看见虚怪的人
And you're the only one who can see the Hollows.
是  我是能看到  但我不是我爷爷
Yeah, see them, sure. But I'm not my grandpa!
我不是他  我不会战斗
I'm not, and I can't fight.
我不会杀人
I can't kill somebody.
我会留下来只有一个原因
There's only one reason that I'd stay here...
拜托
Please.
离开吧
Just go.
杰克  你在这里
Jake? Jakey, there you are.
感谢上帝
Thank God!
当我听到他们找到一具尸体时我吓坏了
When I heard they found a body, I freaked.
这附近有流浪狗吗
Are there stray dogs around here?
你在说什么
What you talking about?
就好像...
It's like...
发现了一只受伤动物的时候
when they find an injured animal,
它们会从最柔软的地方下口
they go for the soft parts first.
同样的事情发生在我父亲身上
Same thing happened to my father.
警察快来了
The police are on their way.
爸爸  我得走了
Look, Dad. I've gotta go.
什么  不  你不能走  杰克
What? No. You don't, Jake.
如果这不是意外事故的话
If this wasn't an accident,
那现在岛上就有个疯子
there's a lunatic on the island.
我这辈子都在跟这岛上的每一个人打交道
I've known everyone on this island my whole life.
除了你和他
Except you, and him.
他在酒馆里坐了一下午了
And he's been in the pub all afternoon.
我也是  我在睡觉
So have I. I was sleeping.
那位盲人朋友呢
What about the blind fellow?
我猜他看不见
I assumed he was blind.
那位戴墨镜的先生
Gentleman with the dark glasses...
跟我搭一班渡轮而来
arrived on the same ferry as me?
我老是看到他在附近转悠
I kept seeing him around.
杰克
Jake!
杰克  等等
Jake! Wait!
你儿子还好吗
Is your son all right?
不好
No.
他有心理健康问题
He has mental health issues.
我走不动了
I can't go.
让我去吧  我经常会跑个五公里
Let me. I run 5-Ks all the time.
有人吗
Hello?
是你吗  年轻人
Is that you, young man?
你过来了
You came through...
你是异能者吗
You're peculiar?
是的
Oh, yes.
我非常感激你
And I'm extremely grateful to you.
最近很难找到时光圈了
Terribly hard to find loops these days.
所以你从沙滩那儿一路跟过来是有目的的
So, you followed me from the beach on purpose?
不是的
Oh, no.
我跟踪你很久了
I've been following you much further than that.
戈兰医生
Doctor Golan?
有的时候
Sometimes.
我觉得时机成熟
When it suits me.
我掌握异能的水平
The breadth of my peculiarity...
完全局限于我的想像力
is purely limited by my imagination.
我唯一无法改变的东西
The only thing I can't change...
就是我的眼睛
is my eyes.
巴伦先生  你好吗
Mr. Barron. How do you do?
我在你爷爷家见过你
I saw you at your grandfather's.
我原本希望能从
I was hoping to get
他那里得到佩格林小姐的地址
Miss Peregrine's address from him.
但是  我的旅伴
But, alas, my traveling companion
在我之前找到了他
got to him before I did.
你也知道...
As you know...
一只饥饿的虚怪是无法阻挡的
there's just no stopping a hungry Hollowgast!
说起我的旅伴
Speaking of my traveling companion...
他马上就到
he's coming.
相信我
Believe me when I say to you...
等他来了  你是不会想
you don't want to be here...
留在这里的
when he arrives.
那我们走吧
So, let's be on our way.
请吧
Shall we?
抱歉
Excuse me.
等等我
Wait for me.
我可不能忘了我们的日历
I mustn't forget our calendar.
劳驾你到客厅把它拿来好吗
Could you fetch it from the parlor
艾沃赛特女士
please, Miss Avocet?
去帮帮其他人
Go and help the others.
佩格林小姐  终于见到你了
Miss Peregrine, what a pleasure
不胜荣幸
to meet you at last!
我们能进来吗
May we come in?
孩子们
Children!
请你们移步到楼下来  好吗
Would you make your way down the stairs, please?
在这座房子里由我发号施令  巴伦先生
I give the orders in this house, Mr. Barron.
现在不是了
Not today.
你应该清楚杰克已经没用了
You should know that Jake has served his purpose.
如果你在乎他的小命  我建议
If you value his life, I suggest
每个人都照我说的去做
everyone does as they're told.
-孩子们  -安静
- Children! - Shush!
没有人可以对我的孩子们下令
No one tells my children what to do!
孩子们
Children...
请下来
come down here, please.
佩格林小姐
Miss Peregrine...
我记得我说过让你安静
I thought I told you to be quiet.
孩子们
Children...
为了杰克的安危
for Jake's safety...
我们要按照巴伦先生的要求去做
we're going to do what Mr. Barron asks.
他希望带我一起回到
He wishes to take me with him
他在黑池的集结地
to his rendezvous in Blackpool.
因此  为了他的安全
So, for his protection...
他想让我化成鸟的形态
he'd like me to assume bird form,
最好关进笼子里
preferably caged.
他想让你们进到一间能上锁的房间里去
He'd like you to make your way into a lockable room,
比如说客厅
such as the parlor...
他不会放了杰克
as he won't release Jake if he fears
他担心一旦失去了筹码
an attack could be mounted upon him...
自己就会遭受攻击
once he loses his leverage.
我说的对吗  巴伦先生
Correct, Mr. Barron?
你要牺牲自己和大家的生命
You're sacrificing yourself and all of us...
去救杰克
for Jake?
巴伦先生是和一只虚怪一起来的  伊诺克
Mr. Barron travels with a Hollow, Enoch.
一旦它到了这里  我们都会死
Once it arrives here, we're all dead.
伊诺克  只有杰克能看到它们
Enoch. Only Jake can see them.
她是说他是我们唯一的希望
She means he's our only hope.
能照顾你们
It's been my privilege...
是我的荣幸
to care for you all.
再见  我的孩子们
Goodbye, my children.
现在  放了他
Now let him go.
答应我一件事  杰克
Promise me one thing, Jake.
答应我你会尽力照顾他们所有人
That you will try to look after them all.
我答应你
I promise.
天快黑了
It's getting dark.
你们甚至连它们的影子都看不到
You won't even be able to see their shadows.
我们必须留在室内
We have to stay inside.
只有在室内我们才有希望
It's the only place we stand a chance.
他说得对  谁知道
He's quite right. Now, where does
佩格林小姐把武器放在哪儿了
Miss Peregrine keep her weapon?
在那里  我们走
In there. Let's go.
好了  孩子们
Now, all right, children.
确认所有房门都锁上了
Make sure all the doors are locked,
所有窗户都闩上了
and the windows are latched.
所有入口都必须封死了  快
Everything must be sealed up tight. Now quickly.
快  行动
Quickly! Go!
给
Here.
杰克  我想今晚最好由你来接电话
Jake, I think tonight, you better answer that.
好
Okay.
你好
Hello?
你好  我是亚伯
Hello, this is Abe.
你是哪位
Who's that?
你还不认识我  我是杰克
You don't know me yet. I'm Jake.
你是新来的  欢迎来到大家庭  杰克
Ah, you're new. Welcome to the family, Jake.
我不能长聊
Now, I can't talk long...
请转告佩格林小姐
so just tell Miss Peregrine...
我在空军基地  我过得很好
I'm at the air base, and I'm fine.
我只想说我很想你
I just wanted to say that I miss you...
还有如果我让你失望了
and if I disappointed you...
对不起
I'm sorry.
你是世界上最好的爷爷
You're the best grandpa in the world.
快点
Quickly.
-菲奥娜  -好嘞
- Fiona. - Got it.
艾沃赛特女士
Miss Avocet.
好了  孩子们
Now, children.
大家到齐了  我们定一些规矩
Now that you're all here, there's a few rules.
安全第一
Your primary job is to stay safe.
虚怪交给我
Leave the Hollow to me.
我不想看到任何逞英雄的行为
I don't want to see any heroics.
现在  拿着园艺工具的那些人
Now those of you with garden tools...
我必须强调  你们要
I must insist that you...
不要  伊诺克  回来
No, Enoch. Get back!
走  到阁楼去
Go. Get to the attic!
快走
Come on!
接着她
Take her.
走  出去
Go. Get out!
奥利芙  快
Olive, come on!
好
Okay.
好了
All right, uh...
糟糕  快要重置了
Crap! It's almost reset!
菲奥娜  你能对那棵树做些什么吗
Fiona, is there anything you can do with that tree?
-能  -当心
- Yes. - Be careful.
我们得翻过那些窗户
We're going through the windows.
我们走  快
Let's go! Quickly!
走
Come on!
克莱儿  下来
Claire, come on down.
来
Come on!
当心啊
Be careful.
走  菲奥娜
Go, Fiona!
我们走
Let's go!
-那是不是  -时光圈关闭了
- Was that... - The loop closing.
它没了
It's gone.
1943年9月3日
抱歉  杰克
I'm sorry, Jake.
现在我们怎么办
What do we do now?
有巴伦和佩格林小姐的迹象吗
Is there any sign of Barron and Miss Peregrine?
已经离开了  巴伦一定有条船
Gone. Barron must have had a boat.
我们得追上他们
We have to go after them.
他带她去黑池了
We know he's taking her to Blackpool.
但是黑池离这里很远
But Blackpool is miles away.
下一班渡轮还要很久才离港
The next ferry doesn't go for hours.
我们赶不上的
We'll never make it in time.
除非我们也坐船去
Not unless we go by boat, too.
所以  在黑池有一个时光圈
So, there's a loop here in Blackpool.
六个月前才刚出现  在2016年1月11日
It's only six months old. January 11th, 2016.
艾沃赛特女士死了  它就无法被重设
With Miss Avocet gone, it can't be reset.
时光圈也不会关闭吧
Won't the loop close?
然后它就回到了现实时间
Then it's back to real time.
杰克  你明白那意味着什么  对吧
Jake, you know what this means, don't you?
你们会死去
You're gonna die.
我不是指这个
That's not what I mean.
我们得回到自己的时间里去
We have to get to our own time,
但你不用
but you don't.
你可以继续在2016年生活
You can continue to live in 2016.
可我为什么要那样做呢
But why would I do that?
如果我们杀了巴伦
If we kill Barron...
他就消失了  但时间会继续
he'll be gone, but time will carry on.
他就去不了弗罗里达了
He won't go to Florida...
亚伯也不会死  你就可以回家了
Abe won't die, and you can go home.
我就能见到我爷爷了
I could see my grandpa.
听着  我能对他们解释这一切
Listen, I can explain everything to them.
能够说服他们带我去岛上
I can persuade them to take me to the island and...
等等  你还会在这里吗
Wait, will you still be there?
我们的旧时光圈永远消逝了
Our old loop's gone for good.
我们不会再见面了
We wouldn't see each other again.
我以为你希望我留下
I thought you wanted me to stay.
我知道你会选择亚伯的
I know you'll choose Abe.
如果我介意的话我就不会告诉你了
If I minded, I wouldn't have told you.
你在地图上找到艾沃赛特女士的
So, have you found Miss Avocet's
时光圈了吗
loop on the map yet?
在这里  不过是新的
It's here. But it's new.
她在今年早些时候制造的  是我所在的年份
She made it early this year. That's my year.
如果我们不在时光圈关掉之前出去
If we don't get out before it closes,
我们就会永远困在2016年1月
we're stuck in January 2016.
好极了
Great.
我们的时间都会走到头
Time catches up with all of us,
除了你我们都会死  计划是什么
we all die, except you. Plan?
时光圈会在四点半关闭
The loop closes at 4:30.
意味着我们要进入时光圈
That means we need to get in,
救了时鸟之后再出来
rescue the Ymbrynes and then get out.
如果我们都还能活着的话
Yeah, if we're not already dead.
艾沃赛特女士说机器
Miss Avocet said the machine is in the cellar
在黑池塔大楼的地下室
of the Blackpool Tower building.
这意味着我们会待在室内  和虚怪一起
That means we will be indoors... with Hollows.
不会的  我有个计划
No, we won't. I've got a plan.
但我需要你们的帮助
But I'm gonna need your help.
不会是在这里吧
This can't be it, can it?
时光圈的入口可能在任何地方
Loop entrances can be anywhere.
伦敦的那个是在一个地铁隧道里
The one in London's in a subway tunnel.
你确定就是这个地方吗
Are you sure this is it?
我觉得是的
I think so.
米勒德  你要先做一件事
Millard, there's something I need you to do first.
好吧  我知道
All right. I know.
快看  塔就在那儿  并不远
Look. There's the tower. It's not far.
你说得轻巧  我快冻死了
Easy for you to say. I'm freezing.
准备好了吗
Ready?
所有通往地下室的门都锁住了
All of the doors to the cellar are locked.
要找到时鸟只能从那里进去
The only way to reach the Ymbrynes is through there.
那里是后台
It's backstage.
你能看到多少只虚怪
How many Hollows can you see?
就四只  还好
Four. That's good news.
我觉得我们两个
I think you and I have
对于还好的定义完全不同
a very different definition of good news.
只有四只就说明巴伦其他的朋友们还没来
It means Barron's other friends haven't arrived yet.
他们还没有开始实验
So they haven't started the experiment.
我们来得还不算晚
We're not too late.
艾玛
Okay, Emma.
你准备好了吗  你知道要说什么
You ready? You know what to say.
绳子在这儿  杰克
Here, Jake.
我们的兄弟应该很快就会来了
Our brethren should be joining us momentarily.
今天我们要
This is a day to...
下面那个
You down there!
我们杀了你的虚怪朋友  巴伦先生
We killed your Hollow friend, Mr. Barron.
现在我们要来救佩格林小姐
And now we've come for Miss Peregrine.
五分钟以内把她和
Bring her and all the other Ymbrynes
其他所有时鸟带到码头
to the end of the pier in five minutes...
不然后果自负
or face the consequences.
这些小孩真是
These children must be
和他们的校长一样疯狂
as insane as their headmistress.
不过虚怪们肯定很高兴能饱餐一顿
Still, the Hollows will be glad of a feed.
你们在哪儿
Where are you?
我知道你们肯定在这里的某个地方
I know you're in here somewhere!
很好  听我说
Good. Listen to me.
我要你们跟着阿彻先生和克拉克先生
I want you to follow Mr. Archer and Mr. Clark.
他们会带你们到码头
They're going to take you down to the pier...
吃顿下午茶
for a little afternoon tea.
阿彻先生  克拉克先生
Mr. Archer, Mr. Clark...
把虚怪们召集过来  带它们去码头
gather the Hollows and take them to the pier.
那些小孩把马尔萨斯杀了吗
Those children killed Malthus?
自从马尔萨斯杀了亚伯·波特曼
Barron's had it in for Malthus
巴伦就一直对马尔萨斯怀恨在心
ever since he killed Abe Portman.
我跟踪了亚伯·波特曼几个月了
I tracked Abe Portman for months.
我只需要几分钟
All I needed was a few minutes...
就能从他那儿搞到佩格林小姐的时光圈的位置
to get the location of Miss Peregrine's loop from him.
但是事与愿违
But no!
马尔萨斯连几分钟都等不了
Malthus couldn't wait.
结果
Instead...
我不得不假扮成一个精神病医生
I had to masquerade as a psychiatrist...
整整三个礼拜
for three weeks...
在佛罗里达
in Florida!
你去过佛罗里达吗
Have you ever been to Florida?
我不是叫你们去召集虚怪吗
Did I not tell you to gather the Hollows?
如果这是个陷阱怎么办
What if it's a trap?
这当然是个陷阱  爱德华兹小姐  但又怎样
Of course, it is, Miss Edwards. But what of it?
几个小孩对付四只虚怪
A couple of children against four Hollows.
赶紧把这破事搞定
Let's get this over with.
杰克  我卡住了
Jake, I'm stuck!
快点
Hurry up!
他们来了
They're coming!
我们走
Let's go.
伊诺克  就是现在
Enoch. Now!
砸  快砸
Go! Now!
可以看到它们了
Starting to see them now.
进入第二阶段
Phase two.
艾玛  上
Emma, go.
别光站那儿  抓住他们
Don't just stand there. Get them!
好的  干得漂亮伙计们  该第二步了
All right. Good job, guys. It's time for step two.
救佩格林小姐
Save Miss Peregrine!
这应该算第三步
That's sort of step three.
首先我们要对付巴伦
First, we've got to deal with Barron.
我们走
Come on.
他们现在应该已经回来了
They should've been back by now.
我说了这是个陷阱
I said it was a trap.
如果真的是这样
If that's true...
或许我们现在应该转移时鸟了
perhaps we should move the Ymbrynes now.
你是认真的吗
You're not serious?
我看着不像认真的样子吗
Do I not look serious?
我看着不像是一个搜遍了整个地球
Do I not look like a man who has searched the globe...
就为多吃一颗眼珠
looking for just one more eye to eat...
希望吃了之后能重获人形
in hopes of regaining sufficient humanity...
继续自己的研究的人吗
to return to his research?
我花了这么多年来抓时鸟
A man who's spent years hunting Ymbrynes...
就是为了今晚
in preparation for this night...
在威尔士用了两天  不  是三天
and two, no, three days, in Wales...
假装是在看鸟
pretending to look at birds!
我向你们保证
I assure you...
我不会放任我的命运
I will not stand idly by...
于不顾的
to see my destiny derailed.
休  上吧
Hugh, do it now!
给我回来
Come back here!
抓住他们
Get them!
快走  趴下
Go. Get down!
你觉得你能阻止我吗
You think you can stand in my way?
你  杰克  满足于生老病死
You, Jake, content to age and die...
好像你根本没有异能的天赋一样是吗
as if you had not the gift of peculiarity at all?
我是更高等的生命
I am a higher being.
我掌握了不死的秘诀
I hold the secret to eternal life!
不好意思打断一下
Sorry to interrupt.
什么
What the...
布朗温
Bronwyn.
你又射偏了  杰克
You missed me again, Jake.
看来你的异能不是精确瞄准
I take it accuracy is not your peculiarity.
亚伯就厉害多了
Abe was a much worthier adversary.
不要让他到时鸟那儿去
Don't let him get to the birds.
你务必把你的裁缝介绍给我认识一下
You must put me in contact with your tailor.
时鸟  时鸟  我来啦
Ymbrynes, Ymbrynes! Here I come!
冷吗
Cold?
等到你浑身的血液都冻住吧
Wait till the blood freezes in your veins.
你就打算这样救你朋友吗
That was your attempt to rescue your friend, was it?
杰克
Jake.
我会尽力拖住他的
I'll hold him off as long as I can.
你什么时候才能意识到
When are you going to realize
你用那玩意的准头烂透了
you are a terrible shot with that thing.
找到其他人  我会在时光圈入口和你们碰头的
Get the others. I'll meet you at the loop entrance.
我救你出来
Let's get you out.
最后
Eventually...
你肯定会没气的
you're going to run out of breath.
然后一切就会结束了
And it'll all be over!
你深爱的杰克和佩格林小姐死路一条
Death for your beloved Jake and Miss Peregrine...
而我则是永生
everlasting life for me!
你会得到一块薄荷糖
And a mint for you.
奥利芙
Olive.
很抱歉  奥利芙
I'm so sorry, Olive.
这些年我从来没有感谢过你
All these years, I never appreciated you.
我不知道自己有多幸运
I didn't see how lucky I was.
我太习惯有你的陪伴  我从来没有意识到
I got so used to having you there, I never realized...
你从来没有意识到什么
You never realized what?
找到你的孩子们  创建新的时光圈
Find your children. Create new loops.
杰克
So, Jake...
看来你继承了你爷爷的异能
I see you've inherited your grandfather's peculiarity.
你跟他一样讨人厌
You're just as annoying as he was.
说到亚伯
Speaking of Abe...
如果你在来生看到他
if you should see him in the afterlife...
替我向他问好
give him my regards.
拜托了  我们不能再冒险让他把你带走
Please. We can't risk him taking you again.
伊诺克  其他人在哪里
Enoch! Where are the others?
他们都安全了  奥利芙正把他们带回幽灵列车
They're safe. Olive is leading them back to the Ghost Train.
杰克需要我们  巴伦太强大了
Jake needs us. Barron's too strong.
你已经失去佩格林小姐了
You've lost Miss Peregrine.
你失去了一切  结束了
You've lost everything. It's over.
杰克
Jake?
艾玛
Emma?
不  等等  看  那不是我  是巴伦
No, wait. Look. That's not me. It's Barron.
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
他是巴伦  不  我是杰克
He's Barron. No, I'm Jake.
那是巴伦
That's Barron.
我比杰克打得准
I've got a better shot than Jake.
没弄清谁是谁之前都不准动
So, neither of you move until we sort this.
听我说  我是杰克
Listen to me. I'm Jake.
我在佛罗里达州长大  我想成为探险家
I grew up in Florida and I wanted to be an explorer.
我以为一切都不会改变  因为我很平凡
I thought nothing would ever change because I was ordinary.
这是杰克  抓住巴伦
That's Jake. Get Barron.
不  听着  我跟他说了所有的事
No. Look. I told him all of this.
她曾经是我的心理咨询师
She was my psychiatrist.
你解决他  我来找佩格林小姐
Look, you deal with him. I'll go find Miss Peregrine.
等等
Wait.
我能证明我是我
Look, I can prove that I'm me...
因为我不平凡
because I'm not ordinary.
我能做到别人做不到的事情
I can do something no one else can
我能看到怪物
I can see the monsters.
不  等等  是我
No, wait. It's me!
伊诺克
Enoch!
赶紧走  时光圈要关上了
We need to go. The loop is closing.
对
Yeah.
我们要走了
Those of us who are leaving.
艾玛
Emma.
你爱你的爷爷
You love your grandfather.
不需要什么解释
There's nothing more to explain.
不  我答应了佩格林小姐我会照顾你们的
No, I promised Miss Peregrine I'd look after you all.
她现在受伤了  你们也没有了时光圈
And with her injured, and you without a loop...
她会康复的
She'll recover.
在那之前  我们会待在1943年
Until then, we'll be in 1943.
我们一天天变老
We'll only age one day at a time.
和普通人一样
Like normal people.
那也不是件坏事
Which can be no bad thing.
虚怪怎么办
What about the Hollows?
只要它们还在  你们就不安全
As long as they're out there, you're not safe.
我们不需要你给我们安全感  杰克
We don't need you to make us feel safe, Jake.
因为你让我们感到勇敢
Because you made us feel brave.
而那样更重要
And that's even better.
来吧  大伙儿  走吧
Come on, guys. Let's go.
小老虎
Tygrysku.
然后我们道别
And then we said goodbye...
而时光圈关闭了
and the loop closed.
我很害怕你不在这里
I was so scared that you wouldn't be here.
我再也见不到你
That I'd never see you again.
我很安全
I'm safe.
我要把你的生日礼物给你
Let me give you your birthday present.
爷爷  我的生日还有好几个月
Grandpa, my birthday isn't for months.
你路上用
For your travels.
去找她吧  杰克
Go to her, Jake.
你有地图
You have the map.
你可以回到1943年
You can get back to 1943.
不  即使是这样  他们坐着船
No. Even so, they took a boat.
我不知道他们在哪里
I don't know where they are.
但你知道他们曾经在哪里
But you know where they were.
你没法想象我花了多久才到这儿
You have no idea how long it took me to get here.
离我最近的时光圈在加利福尼亚州的沙漠里
The closest loop was in the California desert.
我用它到达了东京的时光圈
I used it to get to the Tokyo loop.
然后带我到了离现在最近的1942年的时光圈
And that led me to the nearest loop back in 1942...
我在那里加入了海军
where I wound up joining the Navy.
别细问
Don't ask.
然后我花了两个月在伦敦试图
Then I spent two months in London trying to...
准备全速前进
Ready for full speed ahead!